Products

Privacy Policy  
Your Privacy Rights  
Last Updated: January 1, 2023

General
-------

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of Chobani Global Holdings, LLC and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Chobani”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This Privacy Policy describes how we treat data and information about you that Chobani collects and receives through our mobile applications (“Applications”), this website, and other Chobani websites, including our Food Service, Career and Incubator websites, that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “Websites”), and other aspects of Chobani’s business including offline, such as the Chobani Café and Customer Care inquiries.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Chobani does not own or control.

To help you navigate and understand this Privacy Policy, you may use any of the following links to jump to the section that interests you:

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
When you access, use, visit, or browse the Websites or Applications, you accept our current Privacy Policy.

**How We Collect, Use, and Disclose Personal Information**  
_Information Collected_  
We may collect personal information and other information such as name, home address, email address, telephone number, billing and shipping information, products or services purchased or considered, login credentials, identifiers, preferences, demographic information, geolocation information, professional or employment information, material you choose to submit, and non-personal information, such as aggregated information, technological information such as how users interact with our Websites and Applications or other information that cannot reasonably identify you.

_Sources of Personal Information_  
We may collect personal information from you directly when you interact with us, or our Websites and Applications, or from public sources, social media, or third parties such as our service providers. We may also use technological means, such as cookies, web beacons, pixels, gifs, tags to collect information.

_Why Chobani Collects Personal Information_  
We collect and use information for a variety of business and commercial purposes, including to provide, maintain, and improve our business, Websites and Applications, to fulfill transactions with you, to develop new products and services, to personalize our services, content and ads, for promotional and marketing purposes, to communicate with you, for employment purposes, to conduct market research, and to protect our interests.

_Who Chobani May Share Your Personal Information With_  
We may share personal information with service providers who help us process it, business partners such as partners we conduct marketing with, or advertising and analytics providers who help us serve advertising on our Website and third party sites. We may also disclose information for other purposes if permitted by law, such as if we are cooperating with law enforcement.

**Your Preferences**  
You have certain choices about how we use your personal information. You may opt-out of our marketing email or text messages, stop sharing geolocation data, and opt-out of targeted advertising.

**Reviewing, Correcting, or Changing Your Personal Information**  
Subject to some limits, you may access, review, and request correction to your personal information.

**Children**  
We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under 16 years of age.

**Linking to Third-Party Sites**  
We may provide links to third party websites. However, we are not responsible for any third party sites.

**How We Protect Information**  
We use physical, organizational, and technological security measures to help protect the personal information in our possession, but we cannot guarantee the security of any information.

**We may Transfer Personal Inforamtion to Other Countries**  
By providing us with personal information, you understand and expressly agree that we may transfer some or all of that information outside of your country of residence, including to the United States.

**California Privacy Rights**  
If you are a California resident, this section includes information about your privacy rights under California law.

**Mexico Privacy Rights**  
If you are a Mexican resident, this section includes information about your rights under Mexican law.

**Updates to Our Privacy Policy**  
We may change this Privacy Policy. You should review it regularly.

**Alternate Format of Privacy Policy**  
For an alternative format, please visit chobani.com/accessibility-statement.

**Contact for More Information**  
You can contact us at privacy@chobani.com.

Acceptance of Privacy Policy
----------------------------

Each time you access, use, visit, or browse the Websites or Applications, you signify your acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Websites or Applications and must discontinue use of the Websites and Applications immediately. If you provide your personal information to Chobani through other aspects of Chobani’s business including offline, or if you click on Chobani’s digital advertisements on third-party websites or applications, Chobani asks you to review this Privacy Policy, which also governs information collected by Chobani offline and through digital advertising.

How We Collect, Use, and Disclose Personal Information
------------------------------------------------------

**Information Collected**  
_Personal Information_  
Chobani may collect your personal information. Personal information refers to any information that is reasonably capable of being associated with you. This includes, for example, your name, home address, email address, telephone number, billing and shipping information, and preferences for products or services.

_Non-Personal Information_  
Non-personal information refers to data and information that does not personally identify you as the individual to whom the data or information relates, which may include data that (i) is aggregated (that is, relates to a group of individuals) (“aggregated information”), or (ii) cannot reasonably identify or be linked to you (“deidentified information”).

Chobani may gather or create non-personal information in various ways and may share non-personal information publicly and with other third parties. For example, we may share non-personal information with our partners for certain advertising and measurement purposes. We may also use non-personal information to assess trends about the general use of our products and services.

**Sources of Personal Information**  
Chobani may collect your personal information whenever you interact with Chobani, use or access the Websites and Applications, use Chobani’s products or services, request information or materials from Chobani, enter sweepstakes, contests or drawings offered by Chobani, or communicate with us about our products or other questions.

We may also acquire personal information from publicly available sources, social media platforms, and vendors and other third parties that may share your personal information as permitted in their privacy policies.

_Collection Technology_  
We may use Collection Technology to collect and store personal information. “Collection Technology” refers to cookies, web beacons, pixels, gifs, tags and other technologies that may collect information. Collection Technology such as a cookie may store a piece of data on your browser or device, while other forms of Collection Technology may identify your browser or device and/or collect information through other means. When you visit the Websites or use the Applications, or visit another website or application, your browser or device may be exposed to Collection Technology and Collection Technology may be stored on your browser or device.

You may delete and/or refuse the use of certain Collection Technologies, including cookies, by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. You may use the Websites and Applications even if you choose to refuse or delete such Collection Technologies; however, please note that this may affect your ability to use the full functionality of the Websites and Applications and may impact our ability to customize the Websites and Applications for you.

**Why Chobani Collects Personal Information**  
Chobani collects personal information for a variety of purposes, including:  
• To fulfill a transaction requested by you  
• To provide, maintain and improve our business, including our products, services, Websites and Applications  
• To develop new products and services  
• To provide personalized services, including content and ads  
• To offer and administer promotional activities, sweepstakes and contests  
• Measure performance, including conducting market research  
• Communicate with you  
• For employment purposes, including to accept and evaluate employment applications  
• Protect Chobani, our customers, and the public  
• For our marketing purposes or the marketing purposes of our Business Partners (as defined below)  
• Special Circumstances (as defined below)  
• Corporate Transactions (as defined below)

**Who Chobani May Share Your Personal Information With**  
Chobani may share your personal information with third parties, and we obtain your consent prior to sharing when legally required.

_Service Providers_  
Chobani may share your personal information with third parties who work on behalf of, or with, Chobani including service providers, shippers, vendors, payment processors, advertisers, and consultants (collectively, “Service Providers”). These Service Providers may use your personal information as provided in Section 3(c) (Why Chobani Collects Personal Information).

_Business Partners_  
We may share your personal information with third-party business partners, including partners who we conduct joint-marketing activities with, who we offer a co-branded service with, or who help provide our products to consumers (for example, our resellers and distributors) (collectively, “Business Partners”).

_Advertising and Analytics Providers_  
The Websites or Applications may use analytics and advertising services provided by third parties, such as the advertising services of Google Ads, among others (“Analytics and Advertising Providers”). These analytics and advertising services may use Collection Technology to collect and store information about you and your use of the Websites and Applications, which may include the personal information described above. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps, and resources. We may use this for impression reporting, and to learn, on an aggregate basis, about the demographics and interests of people who visit our website or click our advertising. We may also match the personal information we hold with the information of third parties such as a retailer or social media platform, to better serve you with advertising we think may be of interest to you, or to prevent you from seeing our advertisements too often. We may also share personal information to serve advertising to persons we or our suppliers think may be similar to you. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites, and opt out of some of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

For more information about how you can opt-out of certain targeted-advertising, please see Opting Out from Targeted Advertising below.

_Disclosures Under Special Circumstances_  
Chobani may disclose your personal information to third parties: (i) if we are required or permitted to do so by law or legal process; (ii) when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent harm or financial loss, either to us, or to others; or (iii) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity (collectively, “Special Circumstances”). For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, third parties who receive personal information in accordance with this section shall be referred to as “Special Circumstance Recipients.”

_Corporate Transactions_  
We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets, or should any such transaction be proposed (collectively, “Corporate Transactions”). For the purpose of this privacy policy, third parties who receive personal information in accordance with this section shall be referred to as “Corporate Transaction Recipients.”

Your Preferences
----------------

We may offer you certain choices about what personal information we collect, how we use and disclose the information, and how we communicate with you. Below are a few of the choices that we offer.

**Marketing Emails**  
You may choose not to receive marketing emails from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the marketing emails we send. Even if you opt out of receiving such communications, we may continue sending you non-marketing email communications, such as customer inquiries or information about changes in our terms and conditions.

**Marketing Text Messages**  
We will communicate with you via text messages only if you affirmatively opt in to communicate with us by text. After you have opted in, you can opt out at any time from receiving further communications via text by replying “STOP” to any text message you receive from Chobani, or otherwise following the opt-out instructions in our messages.

**Geolocation Data**  
You may stop sharing your location data by adjusting your mobile devices location services settings. For instruction on changing the relevant settings, please contact your service provider or device manufacturer.

**Opting Out from Targeted Advertising**  
Certain companies we work with to serve targeted content and advertisements (including on third-party websites) (collectively, “Internet-Based Ads”) participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) AdChoices Program or other similar programs, and may display an Advertising Option Icon for Interest-Based Ads on the ads that link to an opt-out tool, which allows you to exercise certain choices regarding targeting. You can learn more about the DAA AdChoices Program at youradchoices.com, and may learn about the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada AdChoices Program, and opt-out of certain practices, at youradchoices.ca/choices/. If you prefer not to receive targeted advertisements from us, as described above, please click on the following link: aboutads.info/choices. Please be aware that, even if you are able to opt out of certain kinds of Interest-Based Ads, you may continue to receive standard advertisements from us and targeted advertisements from third parties after clicking the link. You may need to re-click the link if you delete Collection Technology or use a different computer or browser.

At this time, Chobani does not alter the practices detailed herein based upon your selection of the “Do Not Track” setting or other “opt out” settings or features that may be offered by your browser.

Reviewing, Correcting, or Changing Your Personal Information
------------------------------------------------------------

To review, correct or change your personal information collected by Chobani, please send your request, including the Website, Application, or line of business to which your request pertains, to privacy@chobani.com.

Please note that in some cases we may not be able to allow you to access certain personal information in certain circumstances, for example if it contains personal information of other persons or for legal reasons, including where the information is subject to legal privilege.

We may ask you for information to allow us to confirm that the person making the request is you or is authorized to access your personal information before granting access. For example, we may require you to verify your identity before you access your personal information.

Children
--------

The Websites and Applications are not directed to individuals less than 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under 16 years of age. If you are a parent or guardian and believe Chobani may have inadvertently collected personal information from your child, please notify Chobani immediately by sending an email, including the Website and Application or line of business to which your request pertains, to privacy@chobani.com.

Linking to Third-Party Sites
----------------------------

We may provide links to other websites, services, and applications, such as Facebook and Twitter, that are not operated or controlled by Chobani (collectively, “Third-Party Sites”). Chobani endeavors to link only to reputable organizations. Because these Third-Party Sites may not be hosted or controlled by Chobani, however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites or the content provided thereon.

We encourage you to review and understand the privacy practices of any Third-Party Sites before providing any information to or through them as such practices may differ from those applicable to our Websites and Applications. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected and maintained by Chobani.

How We Protect Information
--------------------------

Chobani maintains reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information and including physical, organizational, and technological security, to help protect the information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. Personal information may be accessed by persons within our organization, or any of our third party service providers or the other persons described in this Privacy Policy, who require such access to carry out the purposes we describe in this Privacy Policy, or that are otherwise required or permitted by law. Personal information we collect is managed from our offices located in New York, New York, United States of America.

Please be aware that the Websites and Applications are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond Chobani’s control.

Chobani cannot guarantee the security of the information on and sent from the Websites and Applications or any other information we receive or collect. No transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure, and there is a possibility for any security measures to be overcome. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Chobani to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. Neither Chobani nor any of our Service Providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. Chobani shall not be responsible for the acts or omissions of any third parties.

We may Transfer Personal Information to Other Countries
-------------------------------------------------------

We may process personal information in, or transfer it to, other countries, including the United States, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as your jurisdiction. We reserve the right to transfer your information to and from any state, province/territory, country or other governmental jurisdiction. As a result of such transfer, your personal information may be subject to access requests by law enforcement and government entities in accordance with the laws of the jurisdictions where the information is stored or processed.

California Privacy Rights
-------------------------

This section applies solely to California consumers and does not apply to Chobani personnel. This section uses certain terms that have the meaning given to them in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 and its implementing regulations (the “CCPA”).

**Notice of Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
We may collect (and may have collected during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Privacy Policy) the following categories of personal information about you:

• **Identifiers:** identifiers such as real name, postal address, email address, phone number, login credentials, or other similar identifiers.  
• **Demographic Information:** demographic information such as your age, gender, or household income information.  
• **Commercial Information:** commercial information, including billing and shipping information, record of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.  
• **Online Activity:** internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with websites, applications or advertisements.  
• **Geolocation Data:** You may stop sharing your location data by adjusting your mobile devices location services settings. For instruction on changing the relevant settings, please contact your service provider or device manufacturer.  
• **Employment Information:** professional or employment related-information, such as information you may provide in connection with an employment application.  
• **Inferences:** inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile to reflect your personal preferences.  
• Additional Content: photographs, comments, reviews, and articles you may submit directly to us or post on the Websites and Applications.

We may use (and may have used during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Privacy Policy) your personal information for the purposes described in our Privacy Policy and for the following business purposes specified in the CCPA:

• Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytics services, or providing similar services  
• Auditing related to a current interaction with you and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance  
• Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction  
• Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity  
• Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality  
• Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration  
• Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us.

**Sources of Personal Information**  
During the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Privacy Policy, we may have obtained personal information about you from the following categories of sources:

• Information you provide to us, including online and offline  
• Collection Technology  
• Publicly accessible sources  
• Business Partners  
• Advertising and Analytics Providers  
• Service Providers  
• Social Media Platforms  
• Other third parties you may use to interact, directly or indirectly, with Chobani

**Sale of Personal Information**  
We do not sell your personal information in exchange for monetary consideration. We may allow certain third parties (such as online advertising services) to collect your personal information via automated technologies on our Websites and Applications in exchange for non-monetary consideration. We share the categories of personal information listed below for online advertising purposes. You have the right to opt-out of this disclosure of your information, which may be considered a “sale” under California law.

During the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Privacy Policy, we may have sold the following categories of personal information about you to online advertising services:  
• Identifiers  
• Online Activity  
• Inferences

We do not have actual knowledge that we sell personal information of minors under 16 years of age.

**Sharing of Personal Information**  
During the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Privacy Policy, we may have shared your personal information with certain categories of third parties, as described below.

We may have disclosed the following categories of personal information about you for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |
|     | Special Circumstance Recipients |
|     | Corporate Transaction Receipts |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Demographic Information | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Commercial Information | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Online Activity | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Geolocation data | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Employment Information | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |
|     | Special Circumstance Recipients |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Inferences | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |
|     | Special Circumstance Recipients |

| Category of Personal Information | Category of Third Party |
| --- | --- |
| Additional Content | Service Providers |
|     | Business Partners |
|     | Advertising and Analytics Providers |
|     | Special Circumstance Recipients |

In addition to the categories of third parties identified above, during the 12-month period prior to the effective date of this Privacy Policy, we may have shared personal information about you with the following additional categories of third parties:  
• Special Categories Recipients  
• Corporate Transaction Recipients  
• Other Third Parties (e.g., content posted may be shared publicly, both on our Websites and on third-party websites)

**California Consumer Privacy Rights**  
You have certain choices regarding your personal information, as described below.

**Request to Know**  
You have the right to request, twice in a 12-month period, that Chobani disclose to you the personal information we have collected, used, disclosed, and sold during the past 12 months.

**Request to Delete**  
You have the right to request that Chobani delete certain personal information we have collected from you.

**Request to Opt-Out of Sale**  
You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information by Chobani.

**Shine the Light Request**  
You also may have the right to request that we provide you with (a) a list of certain categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year and (b) the identity of those third parties.

**How to Submit a Request**  
You may submit a Request to Know or a Request to Delete by contacting us at this toll-free number, +1 (888) 914-9661, PIN 611 362, or by using this interactive webform. To submit a Shine the Light request, email us at privacy@chobani.com. To opt-out of the sale of your personal information, click here or contact us at this toll-free number +1 (888) 914-9661, PIN 611 362. To submit a request as an authorized agent on behalf of a consumer, please email us at privacy@chobani.com and provide (A) evidence that the agent is a business entity registered with the California Secretary of State to conduct business in California and (B) permission to submit the access or deletion request on the consumer’s behalf, signed by the consumer. For questions or concerns about our privacy policies and practices, please contact us as described in the Contact for More Information section of our Privacy Policy.

**Verifying Requests**  
To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your personal information or complying with your request. We will verify your Request to Know or Request to Delete by matching your name and email address you provide in your request against the name and email address we have in our system.

**Additional Information**  
If you choose to exercise any of your rights under the CCPA, you have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment by us. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may charge a reasonable fee to comply with your request.

Mexico Privacy Rights
---------------------

**Collection Technologies**  
Through the Collection Technologies mentioned in this Privacy Policy we may gather data regarding your preferences, the amount of time you spend on our Websites and Applications, your browsing activity and your behavior as a consumer. We use this information to provide you better functionality on our Websites and Applications.

**Why we collect personal information**  
We collect personal information for a variety of primary and secondary purposes, including to fulfill a transaction requested by you, operational or other notified purpose including, to detect security incidents and protect against fraudulent or illegal activity. **“Primary purpose”** means the use of the information for purposes that are necessary and gave origin to the legal relationship we have with you, as well as for our marketing purposes or the marketing purposes of our Business Partners (as defined in this Privacy Policy), or to provide, maintain, and improve our business, including through our Websites and Applications. **“Secondary purpose”** means the use of personal information for different purposes than those that are necessary and gave origin to the legal relationship we have with you and refers to when we use personal information to advance our commercial or economic interests including, for example, by encouraging others to purchase our products and services.

The following are primary purposes for which your personal information may be collected:  
• To fulfill a transaction requested by you  
• Communicate with you  
• For employment purposes, including to accept and evaluate employment applications  
• Protect Chobani, our customers, and the public  
• Special Circumstances  
• Corporate Transactions

The following are secondary purposes for which your personal information may be collected:  
• To provide, maintain and improve our business, including our products, services, Websites and Applications  
• To develop new products and services  
• Provide personalized services, including content and ads  
• To offer promotional activities, sweepstakes and contests  
• Measure performance, including conducting market research  
• Marketing purposes

In case you want to deny your consent for us to process your data for Secondary Purposes, please complete the form available here and submit the completed form to privacy@chobani.com.

Sometimes, we may gather your personal data indirectly, for example, from a transference and/or when it is publicly available. In case you want to manifest your denial for us to process such data, you have 5 business days to do so before we start processing it. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you may revoke your consent at any time.

**Who We May Share Your Personal Information with**  
We may share your personal information with Service Providers and make Disclosures Under Special Circumstances for which we do not require your consent as provided in Article 37 of the FDPL as defined below .

Additionally, we may share your personal information with Business Partners and Advertising and Analytics Providers, for which we require your consent.

In case you wish to deny your consent for us to transfer your data to Business Partners, Advertising and Analytics Partners, please complete the form available here and submit the completed form to privacy@chobani.com.

**ARCO Rights**  
The Federal Law for the Protection of Private Parties Held by Private Parties (the “FDPL”) affords Mexico residents certain rights over their Personal Information, subject to certain exceptions. This section outlines those rights and provides information about how Mexico residents can exercise those rights:

• Access: You have the right to access the information we have from you.  
• Rectification: You have the right to rectify or correct your personal data when it is incorrect or incomplete.  
• Cancellation: You have the right to cancel your personal data from our database.  
• Opposition: You have the right to oppose to the treatment of your data for specific purposes.

_How to Submit an ARCO Rights Request_  
You may submit a Request to exercise your ARCO Rights by completing the form available here and submitting the completed form to privacy@chobani.com. We will verify your request by matching your name and email address you provide in your request against the name and email address we have in our system.

You may designate an authorized agent to make an ARCO Request on your behalf in accordance with the FDPL. We may require that you provide the authorized agent with written permission to act on your behalf and that the authorized agent verify their identity directly with us.

At all times you should submit the following information in order for us to process your request: (i) name, domicile and/or any other media to communicate the response to your request; (ii) documents accrediting your identity or the identity of your legal representative; (iii) a clear and precise description of the personal data over which you seek to exercise any of the ARCO Rights; (iii) any other element or document that facilitates the location of the personal data; and (iv) when you seek to rectify your personal data, the indication of the modifications and the documents supporting such modifications.

We will communicate our response to your ARCO Rights request in a maximum of 20 days counted as of the first day we receive your request, and, if appropriate, your rights will be made effective within the next 15 days as of the day when we communicated the corresponding response. Please bear in mind that the referred terms may be extended for the same periods of time once, as long as the circumstances are justified

_How to Submit a Request to revoke my consent_  
You may submit a Request to Revoke my consent by completing the form available here and submitting the completed form to privacy@chobani.com. Please note that if you revoke your consent for us to process your personal information it may make it impossible for us to provide our Services to you.

_How to limit the use and/or disclosure of your data_  
If you wish to limit the use and/or disclosure of your data, you may enroll in the Federal Registry to Avoid Publicity of the Federal Agency for Consumer Protection through this link: repep.profeco.gob.mx

The domicile of the data controller is located in the State of New York, United States of America.

Updates to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

The Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time. We display a last updated date at the top of the Privacy Policy for you to know when there has been a change. Accordingly, you should check the Privacy Policy on a regular basis for the most current privacy practices.

Any changes in the Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting. If Chobani makes any material changes to this Privacy Policy, Chobani will provide you with notice or have other communications with you in the manner and to the extent required by law.

Alternate Format of Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

To access this statement in an alternative format, please visit chobani.com/accessibility-statement

Contact for More Information
----------------------------

If you have any questions or concerns about Chobani’s privacy policies and practices, please email us at privacy@chobani.com or call us (212) 364-6490.

You may also write to our Chief Legal Officer and General Counsel at 200 Lafayette Street, New York, New York 10012.

Chobani, LLC

Attention: General Counsel, 669 County Road 25, New Berlin, New York 13411

Get the freshest Chobani news

​Subscribe

placeholder

By checking the box, you agree that you are at least 18 years of age.placeholder

Choose region

​

© 2024 Chobani, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

Get the freshest Chobani news

Subscribe

placeholder

By checking the box, you agree that you are at least 18 years of age.placeholder

Choose region

​

Choose region

​

© 2024 Chobani, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *
